Hello friends, I am Vishal Malode, I
welcome you all with all my heart. Today we are
going to see how we can
join ICICI Bank. We are going to see all the eligibility criteria and examination pattern required for this, which is a
probationary officer program of ICICI Bank. Let's
start. First of all,
we are going to open a browser. You
can open any browser. There you have to type
ICICI Bank
Career. This is the official website of ICICI Bank.
After clicking on it, this page opens and
after that we are going to click here. New
User. Those who have come to this portal for the first time,
they have to
click on New User. After clicking on New User,
a form will be displayed.
You have to fill up that form here.
The site has been opened. This is a
form. It has four steps:
Upload Resume, Personal Details, Academic
Information, Work Experience and
Supplementary
Information. Here you will find important information.  That is, your
resume, whether
you are working or
fresher, both are eligible
to apply, so here you have to
upload your resume,
then you have to fill up your basic details
here, the
email ID that is given is very
important, fill the email ID carefully
and then the mobile number and email ID are very important,
all the communication is
done through email and mobile, so these two things are
very important, then the
academic information, whether it is your
graduation details or post-graduation
details, you have to fill up here, the work
experience, whether you are a fresher
or working, you
can mention it, then you have to
upload some documents in the supplementary information, you can upload those
documents and fill up this form
completely successfully,
after that,
after filling up this form successfully, we will see what is
required for this.  Eligibility
Criteria Now we are going to see on their official
website
what is the eligibility criteria, then we are going to go back to ICICI
Bank Career,
here their page is open, here is
ICICI Bank Manipal Probationary Officer
Program, okay, then after you click on this,
that page opens,
here they have given
three eligibility criteria, one is
education qualification marks and
your age, your minimum is
graduation complete and
for that you need to have at
least 55% marks in graduation and the age
limit is 27 years of age, you should not be
more than 27
years of age, at the time when
you are going to submit the form,
then we will see
how the examination pattern selection process is, there
are two steps in it, the
first step is online aptitude
test, in this online aptitude test we
will see what factors come in it  There
are three parts, Verbal Quantity Aptitude and Logical Ability, on
which the exam is conducted. This exam is conducted
online. When I
joined ICICI Bank, this
exam was not online. It was offline. But
now all the facilities have been provided.
So, everything has shifted to online.
Okay, this exam is usually of 60
minutes. In this 60-minute exam, there
are about 60 questions
and there is no negative marking. The
important part is that
after passing this exam, you are
not called for a personal interview, but the personal
interview is also scheduled for you online
and you are informed about it through email.
For this,
you need to provide your correct email ID.
After completing all this process, you are eligible for ICICI Bank Professional
Officer. For this,
you are called to Bangalore. There is
some classroom training there, followed by
on-the-job posting.
All these details will be given in the next section.  In the video, I
will tell you the advantages and disadvantages of joining ICICI Bank.
Let's see all this in the next
video. If
you liked this video, then definitely
like and share it. Thank you.